When did I fall asleep?
The pact shouldn't have expired yet.
Sir Piggymaru?
What's the matter?
What's up, Piggymaru?
Oh, did I wake you?
Nah, don't worry about it.
The resident of this room might be out.
Did you hear that just now?
Yes.
- Get back!
- Right!
A skeleton king!
This thing?
It's leagues above the other monsters here.
Sir Hati!
We should be able to slay it
if we shatter that silver part below its chin!
That's its weak spot, huh?
This monster is too much
for your average soldier to handle.
It's so strong that even the Saber Tigers
might just barely be able to take it.
Looks like it considers Mist
the real threat here.
Now, how shall we attack?
Sir Hati, I have a request.
I'm about to use a certain power
to improve my base physical abilities
and create unique armaments.
I'd like to keep this power
a secret as long as I can,
so could you please keep what
you're about to witness between us?
Yeah, this thing's definitely strong.
Also, my apologies in advance.
Should this monster exceed my expectations,
I might not be able to protect you.
So if it comes down to it, please run—
Paralyze!
Rather, it's only strong compared
to the rest of these ruins.
Poison!
THE CHAIN KNOWN AS TRUST
Good. Looks like this was the right thing.
You mean that skeleton king was the monster
you were searching for, Sir Hati?
Yeah.
Once we return to the surface,
I'll answer any questions I can.
Did my face give me away?
What's up, Piggymaru?
There's something over there?
What's this?
Some kind of magic cloth or something?
An egg?
What is it, Piggymaru?
You're interested in the egg?
You want to take it home with us?
All right.
If that's what you want,
I'll see what I can do.
Well, shall we head back to the surface now?
It's skeleton knights!
Run!
This isn't happening! It can't be!
- I lost my hand!
- Sakura-san, hang in there!
Th-The goddess might heal it for you!
Can I do it with this weapon?
No, I must!
- I have to buy time for
everyone to escape and—
- Hands off, Ayaka!
Bullet!
RED FIST SHOT
BULLET
Draconic Buster!
GOLDEN DRAGON BLAST
DRACONIC BUSTER
There's no denying they're strong foes.
However, I was simply stronger.
With that, I've reached level 24.
I-Is this the Dragon Eye Chalice?!
Is it actually the real thing?!
At any rate, this concludes
my business in the Mils Ruins.
Sir Hati!
I was watching from afar,
but that was quite a commotion.
There's going to be a reception tomorrow
where I receive my reward.
I'll find an inn for another night.
Then I assume you're free
until the reception tomorrow?
Yes.
If possible, I'd like to speak to you alone.
Would either of our rooms work for you?
I don't mind that.
Then how about mine at eight o'clock?
You make decisions swiftly, don't you?
I'll be there.
Once again, thank you very much
for the Dragon Eye Chalice.
Nothing you need to thank me for.
So we have a monster enhancement
solution now, do we?
We'll be using this on you later.
Sir Hati, it's me, Mist.
She's here right at the agreed time.
You want to employ me as your bodyguard?
Yeah, I thought you might be
interested in earning a bit more.
Though maybe you're set on travel funds now
with the reward for the Dragon Eye Chalice.
Indirectly reminding her about that...
Even I feel like this is playing dirty.
You've probably guessed as much,
but my goal is finding the Witch of Taboos.
My destination is the Land
of Golden-Eyed Monsters.
The Land of Golden-Eyed Monsters...
I'm expecting plenty
of swarming monster attacks.
I'd feel better having a skilled
swordsman watching my back,
just like when we were
conquering the Mils Ruins.
I've been considering hiring a warrior
all along to ensure my safety,
and you're a perfect fit.
I'm on a journey to the Duchy of Yonato.
If we head there via the
Land of Golden-Eyed Monsters,
that'd be quite convenient for me.
However...
I'm a little hesitant to agree,
but I have to accept it's necessary
to meet her needs.
No reason to rush the decision.
It sounds like there are other routes
if you're headed to Yonato.
By the way, can I ask something, Seras?
Yes. What is it?
Oh!
E-Er, Sir Hati, um, why did you just...
Sorry for catching you off guard.
So you knew?
Remember falling asleep in the Mils Ruins?
That was the work of my skill.
It was, was it?
You were hesitating earlier
about revealing yourself to me, weren't you?
Traveling together while trying
to hide your identity would be an issue.
Because you can't exactly sleep that way.
Am I wrong?
Y-You're not.
I need your combat prowess.
I've no intent to sell you out.
I use the power of spirits
to conceal my identity.
It requires that I offer up
my desire for sleep in exchange.
Which is why you revert back
to normal when you sleep.
Yes.
I was being chased by those Holy Watchers
because they caught me unawares
and saw my true form.
I have a lot more flexibility in my travels
with those four gone.
I truly am grateful to you.
If you're dismissing your spell around me,
I assume that means you trust me?
Yes, I do, Sir Hati.
I believe you are a man worthy of trust.
Trust, huh?
- It's Touka.
- Huh?
My real name is Touka Mimori.
Please don't share that with anyone else.
In return, I won't reveal your name
to anyone without your consent either.
This is another way to further
bind her to me using trust.
Hati... No, Sir Tooka.
Let me introduce myself again.
I am Seras Ashrain.
ELF, FORMER CAPTAIN OF NEAH'S KNIGHTS
- I will serve as your bodyguard
and accompany you to the
Land of Golden-Eyed Monsters.
Yeah, I'll be counting on you.
Yes.
Here's your payment.
Terribly sorry.
Everything all right?
Um, I was just surprised...
By what?
Sir Tooka, I don't think this could be
anything other than a blue dragon gem.
Blue dragon gem?
Is it something valuable?
It's said that these gems are only rarely born
within legendary blue-eyed dragons.
There's nary a one circulating
on the market right now.
Its value...
easily surpasses the reward
for the Dragon Eye Chalice.
Then it should be satisfactory payment.
You can't, Sir Tooka!
You shouldn't give something
like this away so readily.
Too nice for her own good too, huh?
I said it was yours.
Toss it out if you want.
Huh? Wait, but...
It's sufficient payment
for guarding me, right?
Th-That's true, but...
Very well.
For the time being, please call me
Hati in front of other people.
I'll call you Mist when we're outside too.
Understood.
It might be a little late at this point...
But as you know, I'm on the run.
There's a great deal about me
that I haven't told you yet.
I'm not trying to dig into your past.
As your employer, I just want you
to be in top form as my guard.
I have no intention to pry past that.
You're always considerate
in that fashion, Sir Tooka.
Yeah, well, I'm a nice guy.
Perhaps I should have cleansed myself
before meeting with Sir Tooka earlier.
Tooka Mimori...
I'm not trying to dig into your past.
I want to believe him,
like I did the princess.
Hey, check it out!
Looks like some mercenary's
already won her over.
I heard she was spotted
leaving his room last night.
Let them say what they will.
- So she discovered a taste for men
alongside the Dragon Eye Chalice, eh?
- You're quite mature about that, Sir Hati.
By the way, have you ever
heard of forbidden magic?
Yes, I have.
First unimportant discovery:
Seras apparently has a tendency
to touch her chest while talking.
Said magic is forbidden according
to Goddess Vicius.
It's generally understood
to be specific ancient spells.
In other words,
these spells are now forbidden
because the goddess said so.
Indeed, we can assume they are
forbidden by her decree.
Magic the goddess outlawed...
That's bound to mean it's
spells that are dangerous to her.
My apologies. That's about all I know.
No, that's plenty.
Thank you.
I-If I managed to be of help, I'm glad.
Need you be so deferential
over a simple thanks?
I think it's the first time you've
given me a frank thank you.
I was feeling a bit bashful.
They said it would be a morning reception.
I should be back by one
in the afternoon at the latest.
Then I'll be outside the inn
a little after noon.
Very well.
I shall see you then, Sir Hati.
All right, let's start the enhancement
experiment, Piggymaru.
Thank you all for gathering here today!
I have invited a mage specialized
in breaking illusions
so that we can ensure the authenticity
of the Dragon Eye Chalice,
recently recovered by Mist Balukas.
Now, let's have a look!
Seras...
ALION CASTLE
- I heard you had a tough time when
the skeleton knights appeared.
Um, what about Sakura-san?
Yes, I'll take care of her.
I'll put her back together with Heal.
I see. You have my thanks.
I can't use it on just anyone, though.
This is only because Miss Sakura is B-class.
By the way, Miss Sogou,
will you not be joining
Mister Kirihara's group?
I can't imagine I'd get along very
well with Kirihara-kun as things stand.
That's what I mean.
I'm saying your selfishness is
disrupting the harmony of Class 2-C.
At least from what I've seen.
M-My selfishness?
Oh, dearie me. Am I wrong?
Is there some rational explanation?
Are you okay?
I-It's not like that! I just...
No, no, it's fine.
This is all the result
of insufficient guidance.
The blame is entirely on me.
Miss Sogou?
I'm sorry.
Even if it is selfish,
I can't team up with Kirihara-kun
as he is now.
Even if that means turning your back
on a world seeking salvation?
I'm fulfilling my duty as an
S-Class hero in my own way!
Very well!
Then I'll entrust the students who couldn't
pass their trials to you, Miss Sogou.
If an S-Class like you trains them,
I'm sure they'll become
as strong as a hundred men.
Hold on just a minute!
We already settled this matter when
I agreed to fight in their stead, right?!
To be honest, we received
a royal decree a few days ago
calling for the disposal
of all heroes who can't fight.
I'm sorry, but I'm powerless to change it.
If I refuse, you'll get rid
of them, won't you?
That's what I'll be forced to do. I'm sorry.
I understand.
Excellent! Take good care of them.
I'll share the details with you later.
Excuse me.
Oh, and just in case...
Know that if they become a hindrance,
you may be forced to reckon
with a cruel reality.
But I'm sure you'll be fine.
Humans always grow stronger
when they face reality.
I thank you for your concern.
That damn bitch.
Either I misjudged her,
or something has happened to Seras.
What's your wager?
If you think she ditched us
without a word, squeal twice.
If you think otherwise, squeal once.
Sounds like we're both leaning
toward a generous read this time.
Not much of a bet that way.
Seras hardly has a motive to disappear on us.
If she didn't want to go with us,
she could've just turned down
the gig to start with.
- And if she meant to deceive us,
- Hey, did you hear?
- she wasted way too much effort.
- The woman who found that Dragon Eye Chalice
was the fugitive Princess Knight!
The woman who found that Dragon Eye Chalice
Yeah, I heard.
Apparently she fled into the Dark Forest.
Let's go! It's paladin hunting time!
I wouldn't do that!
Huh? Why would you say that?
You don't want to get involved.
The—
The Black Dragon Knights?!
THE DARK FOREST
The Black Dragon Knights!
Willozega, Willozega!
Silfigzea!
Thanks to that illusion breaker,
my spirit of light is disoriented.
I can't transform until it recovers.
Just surrender and die,
Seras Ashrain!
If their average knight is this skilled,
what are the troops above them like?
No.
The dragon behind me is a decoy!
My real enemy...
is in front of me!
Well done seeing through that!
My name is Gizun!
I'm vice captain of the squad led
by Sir Orban of the Five Dragoons!
You die here, Seras Ashrain!
I can't use my Spirit Regalia right now.
I'll have to manage with my available spirits.
I thought they would try and take me captive.
Has their stance finally
changed to eliminating me?
If you want to know, fine.
Shall I tell you before you die?
Orban's squad is under secret orders.
You may have features as enticing as honey
and a body that stokes the instincts of men...
but even so, there are still people
in this world who'd see you dead!
I knew it. I'll need my
Spirit Regalia for this foe.
Oh no!
If you're going to kill me,
then make it quick.
We were told to kill you without
doing anything to you,
but rejoice, Princess Knight of a lost nation.
If you haven't known a man yet,
then I'll show you what it means
to be with one before you die!
If only I could use my Spirit Regalia!
Paralyze.
Now, time to have some f—
Hey.
It's long past the time we agreed to meet.
Poison!
INFLICT POISON, POISON
LETHAL
NONETHAL
Too—
What are you doing here?
I came looking for you, of course.
That's not what I'm asking about.
Hold on.
Sleep.
We may have things to talk about that
we don't want anyone overhearing.
I-I'm sorry I didn't consider that.
However, if you remain with me, then...
I'll be pursued by the
Black Dragon Knights too?
Th-That's right!
I'll return the payment you gave me.
So let's nullify our bodyguard agreement.
To be honest, it would be a pain.
I-Indeed. Staying with me
will only cause you trouble.
That's not what I meant.
U-Um, what is this?
Open it and see.
A-Are these all blue dragon gems?!
Well, yeah.
You really are...
I meant it'd be a pain to find a better guard.
Now, Seras...
Take off your clothes.
Huh?
HUMANITY'S STRONGEST, CIVIT GARTLAND